Cover Schwarz and Weiss's entire confrontation in one go?!
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途  台本: 共由 翻译: 新人&poopy  繁化: 謙謙  校对：绫女 时间轴：那年夏天  后期：娜夏
シュバルツとヴァイセの対決を一気に描く
Yes!
はい
And it might not even last 50 chapters?!
それが50回もたないかもしれないと
Yes!
はい
But still,
いや しかし
surely there are many ways to continue the story after you settle the conflict between black and white—
黒対白 その決着がついても続けようはいくらでも
We'd rather have a work that we're satisfied with instead of one that has a long run!
長く続けるよりも 作品として納得のいくものにしたいんです
I see.
なるほど
As your editor, I'd want you to continue your manga for as long as it's popular.
担当として人気があれば
長く続けてほしいという気持ちはあるが
However, if it clearly becomes boring
because you're forced to prolong it, then...
無理に続ける事で明らかにつまらなくなってもなぁ
Okay. Let's put off the decision on whether to end it there or not
分かった そこで終わらせるかどうかは
決着まで描ききったところで考えよう
until after you're done with their confrontation.
Thank you!
ありがとうございます
For now, spend each and every week giving everything you've got on Schwarz and Weiss's showdown!
今はシュバルツとヴァイセの対決を毎週全力で描いていく事
That much I'm sure of!
それだけは間違いない
Yes!
はい
yu
me
Dreams, dreams, dreams, dreams
ka
na
e
ru
ta
bi
ko
wa
re
te
yu
ku
me
As soon as I reach my goals, it all falls through again
na
ze
so
re
de
mo
ma
ta
So why do I run...
bo
ku
wa
sa
ga
su
ha
shi
ri
tsu
zu
ke
ru
...and search in spite of that?
hi
sa
shi
bu
ri
ni
de
atta
We met after such a long time
"
fu
n
i
ki
ka
watta?"
"Has the mood changed for us?"
tsu
ki
hi
wa
na
ga
re
ta
da
rou
So much time has passed
"
a
no
ko
ro
no
ho
u
ga
ta
no
shi
so
u
"
"It seemed like more fun back then"
ta
ku
sa
n
na
ku
shi
ta
We've lost so much
so
n
na
ko
to
wa
ki
zu
i
te
ru
n
da
I already know that, though
sa
ke
bi
tsu
zu
ke
ro
mo
ga
ki
tsu
zu
ke
ro
Don't stop screaming, don't stop struggling
da
re
no
ta
me
ni
na
n
ka
mou
i
da
rou?
You've done enough for others
ma
da
tsu
ta
e
i
ko
to
ga
a
ru
ma
da
I still, still have something I haven't told you yet
yu
me
no
sa
ki
ni
wa
yu
me
shi
ka
na
i
Beyond each of my dreams lies yet another dream
Breather and Party
Oh, this week's Reversi is in first place.
今週は「REVERSI」1位か
It's made a complete recovery.
完全に持ち直しましたね
For the past few weeks, Reversi and Zombie Gun have been hogging the top two spots.
ここ何週かは「REVERSI」と
「ZOMBIE☆GUN」で1位2位独占しちゃってますよ
There's a huge gap between them and third place.
3位以下との差がありすぎるんだよな
That said, the main titles have still been doing well.
と言っても 中堅だって十分しっかりしてるんだが
If we were to bring in a new series right now, I don't think it'd survive long.
今新連載を立ち上げても生き残れる気がしませんよ
Don't sound so hesitant.
そんな弱気でどうする
Think of it this way—if we bring in a new series,
中堅を終わらせるくらいの作品でなきゃ
it had better be good enough to
justify canceling one of the main titles.
連載してもしかたないくらいに思ってやれよ
The serialization committee is on September 27, right?
連載会議9月27日でしたよね
If some new series are brought in, then others will get canceled.
新連載が入ってくれば 終わる作品も
Yup. If we manage to get three new ones,
3本くらい決まったら
the series ending might very well be NATURAL and Seigi no Mikata!
「NATURAL」や「正義の三肩」
だって終わってもおかしくないぞ
Huh?!
I already said that it wouldn't be unusual if one of the main titles gets canceled, right?
中堅が終わってもおかしくないって そういう事だろ
There was a serialization committee today.
今日連載会議があったわけだが
And? You already told me there's no way Never Reaching You would get canceled.
「僕通」は絶対に終わらない そうでしたよね
I did, but there's something else I need to tell
you before we get into what the committee said.
それは そうだが
会議の結果を知らせる前に一つ
Congratulations! Never Reaching You will get an anime!
おめでとう「僕には通じない」のアニメ化が決定した
Mr. Yoshida! You really are a reliable editor!
吉田氏
やっぱりあなたは頼りになる担当だー
I did what you said, and I really did get an anime out of it!
言われたとおりにやってたら 本当にアニメにまで
And after my anime starts, you'll be my love adviser and tell me
アニメになったら 恋のアドバイザー 吉田氏の
the magic marriage proposal that'll make Yuri say yes!
「YES」しか返ってこない
魔法の言葉でユリタンにプロポーズでしたよね
Right? Right?
ねえ　ねえ
No, that's on hold for now.
いや それは延期だ
What?! Are you trying to trick me again, you bastard?
何だと貴様 また俺をだましたのか
No. Aoki's What God Gave Me just got canceled.
違う 蒼樹先生の「神様がくれた」の連載終了が決まったんだ
Huh?
She must be depressed right now.
蒼樹先生は落ち込んでいるに違いない
If you propose to her now, she won't answer favorably.
こんな時にプロポーズしてもいい返事は返ってこない
Yuri's series... Her series is over!
ユリタンの連載が ユリタンの連載が終わる
That's how it is, so as for your proposal...
そういう事なのでプロポーズは そうだな
Well, you'd better wait until she starts another new series.
蒼樹先生がまた連載を始めるまで待つしかないだろう
Yuri... Poor Yuri.
かわいそうなユリタン
I feel bad for Aoki, but this may have saved us.
蒼樹先生には悪いが ある意味助かったかもな
Yuri... It's at times like these when I need to cheer you up.
ユリタン こんな時僕が元気づけてあげなければ
Hello?
はい
G-Good evening.
こ こんばんは
Good evening as well.
こんばんは
What's wrong, Hiramaru?
どうしたんですか 平丸さん
Uh...
え えっと
Um...
Once you've finished drawing What God Gave Me,
「神様がくれた」を描き終えたら 僕と遊園地に行って下さい
please come to the amusement park with me!
W-Won't you come have fun with me at the park?!
ゆ 遊園地で元気に楽しく遊びませんか
Hiramaru...
平丸さん連載が終わる私を元気づけようと
He's trying to cheer me up because my series got canceled.
Yes, I'd be glad to.
はい 喜んで
Really?!
ほんとですか
うわ 僕楽しくなるように頑張りますから
I'll try to make it as fun as I can!
Yes. I'm looking forward to it.
はい 楽しみにしてますね
Hiramaru, it's already been two years since you asked me out.
平丸さん「つきあって下さい」
って言ってから もう2年ですよ
Have we finally gone from meeting over tea to dates at the amusement park?
やっと お茶から遊園地
What?
何 蒼樹先生と遊園地に
You're going to the park with Aoki?
It's "Tea Day" on November 1st.
11月1日 紅茶の日
I wanted to cheer her up.
そこで励まそうと思いまして
I'll have my work all wrapped up before I go, I promise!
そのためならスケジュールもちゃんと詰めます
W-Well, that's great, but...
そ それは助かるが
Well then, I'd better get back to work!
それでは僕は仕事に戻りますので
Aoki at the park! It's gonna be so much fun!
蒼樹さんとの遊園地楽しくするぞー
Crap! This is bad!
まずい こいつはまずいぞ
This is the man who let himself get carried away and confessed to her
2人だけでお茶ができると決まっただけで暴走し
simply because they went out for tea with each other!
告白までしてしまった男だ
At this rate, he's really going to propose to her!
あの調子では本気でプロポーズまでしかねん
And if she turns him down...
それでもし断られたら
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
That would be bad! Really bad!
まずい 非常にまずいぞ
I should stop this from happening.
やはり阻止すべきか 平丸君のためにも
For his sake!
For his... sake?
平丸君のため
Hiramaru Kazuya. 26 years old, single.
平丸一也 26歳 独身です
It's a pleasure to meet you.
よろしくお願いします
Well, have a seat.
まあ 座って下さいよ
Okay.
はい
So, apparently you wrote this Otter #11 in a month
この「ラッコ11号」
without ever having read manga before. Is that right?
マンガ読んだ事ないのに ひとつきで描いたそうだね
Yes.
はい
You're a genius.
君は天才だ
So I'm often told.
よく言われます
They ask, "You can do it if you try, so why don't you?"
やればできる子なのに なぜやらないと
If you stick with me, you can become a popular manga author.
僕とやっていけば大人気マンガ家になれる かもね
Perhaps.
Will life become fun?
生きてる事が楽しくなりますか 幸せになれますか
Can I become happy?
Uh... I think you can? You'll get paid handsomely.
なれるんじゃないかな お金も入るし
Then, make me happy!
じゃあ 幸せにして下さい
Make me happy!
幸せにーして下さいー
What have I actually done for him?
平丸君のために俺は何をしてやったというのだ
He's certainly got the sales figures,
and the wealth and fame to go with it.
確かに売れて 金と名声は手に入ったかもしれない
But... is that really enough?
しかし それだけでいいのか
What's wrong, Mr. Yoshida?
どうしたんです 吉田氏
平丸君 そんなに蒼樹先生が好きか
Hiramaru, do you really love Aoki?
は はい
Yes.
How much?
どのくらいだ
Huh? Are we in middle school or something?
何ですか 中学生みたいな その質問は
How much?!
どのくらいだ
I love her so much that I want to marry her right now!
今すぐ結婚したいくらい好きですよ
決まってるじゃないですか
Isn't that obvious?!
That's it, Hiramaru!
それだ 平丸君
What?
何
"I love you so much that I want to marry you right now!"
「今すぐ結婚したいくらい好きです」これが魔法の言葉だ
Those are the magic words!
You can take out the "I love you so much" bit, though.
ただし「くらい好き」は取っていい
Listen up, Hiramaru!
いいか 平丸君
On November 1st, "Tea Day,"
11月1日 紅茶の日
Hiramaru Kazuya will propose to Aoki Kou, a.k.a. Aoki Yuriko,
平丸一也は蒼樹紅こと青木優梨子に
遊園地でプロポーズするんだ
at the park!
I-I can?
い いいんですか
Can you tell her that, Hiramaru?!
言えるか 平丸
Yes! I'll do my best!
はい 頑張ります
All right!
Date with Yuri at the park!
Hiramaru, this is my first date at an amusement park.
平丸さん 私 遊園地でデートなんて初めてなんです
Mine too.
ぼ 僕も
Well, I've only ever had dates with you, Hiramaru.
って デート自体平丸さんとしかした事ないんですけどね
The park will close shortly.
「間もなく閉園の時間となります」
Oh, right.
そ そうだ
Just before it closes, go ride on the ferris wheel.
閉園間際 最後に観覧車に乗れ
At this time of year, it'll be dark
already and you'll get a nice view.
この季節もはや外は夜景
Right!
It'll set a romantic mood for her answer.
いやおうでも気持ちはロマンチックになる
Yuri, let's ride the ferris wheel!
ユリタン 観覧車に乗りましょう
What? Now?
今からですか
Please!
お願いします
They're finally on the ferris wheel!
ついに観覧車に 時間的には悪く
Not bad, in terms of time—
I told him to sit next to her so many times!
あれだけ隣に座れと言ったのに
I'm gonna bash his face in, dammit!
テンパりやがって あのやろ
わぁ きれい
It's so pretty.
The best time to propose is when your car reaches the top.
観覧車が一番上に行った時がプロポーズの最高のタイミングだ
We'll be at the top soon.
もうすぐ一番上だ この日のために用意した
The item that I've prepared for this day...
...isn't here.
ない 5，000万円の指輪が
The 50 million yen ring!
Yeah! Go for it!
いけ もうすぐだ
You're almost there!
Propose to her!
そこでプロポーズするんだ
It's not here! Or here!
ない ない ないぞ
Here either!
Wh-What's wrong, Hiramaru?
ど どうしたんです 平丸さん
What the heck are you doing, Hiramaru?!
何をやっている 平丸
You've passed the top!
一番上を過ぎてしまったではないか
Please watch your step.
足元にお気を付け下さい
Are you okay, Hiramaru?
大丈夫ですか 平丸さん
ど どこにいったんだ 指輪
Where did the ring go?
Huh? Ring?
指輪
That was Yoshida...
今のは吉田さん
Hiramaru's outfit... Wearing a white suit to an amusement park...
平丸さんの格好
遊園地に純白のスーツ
An obviously worried Yoshida checking up on him...
心配そうに見に来ている吉田さん
And a "ring"...
それに指輪
Um, can we ride it one more time?
あのう もう1周いいですか
But it's closing time already.
でも もう閉園だよ
Please?
お願いします
Go right ahead. Please enjoy yourselves.
どうぞ お幸せに
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
Um, Hiramaru?
あの 平丸さん
Yes?
はい
You have something you'd like to tell me, don't you?
何かお話があるんですね
Hiramaru, you can do it.
平丸さん 頑張って
Try to say it.
頑張って話して下さい
Please, do your best.
頑張って下さい
O-Okay.
Huh? What was I going to say again?!
あれ～ 何て言うんだっけー
I have to say something!
は 早く言わなければユリタンが
「頑張って」って言ってくれてるのに
Yuri's telling me to do my best!
What are you doing, Hiramaru?!
何をしている 平丸
Are you going to let another chance slip you by again?!
また チャンスを逃す気か
Y-Yuri!
ユ ユリタン
Y-Yes?
は はい
P-Ple-Please...
ぼ 僕 僕を
...mmmake me happy!
幸せにして下さい
平丸さんを幸せに
Make you happy?
Yes!
はい
Are you not happy enough being here with me at the park?
私と遊園地に来ていて まだ幸せが足りませんか
No, I mean, marry me and make this happiness permanent...
い いえっ だから結婚して この幸せを永遠のものに
Marry me...
結婚して
and make me happy too, please!
私も幸せにして下さい
I did it!
やったあ
Oh! He's jumping around! You must've done it, Hiramaru!
あのはしゃぎよう やったのか 平丸
Sorry. I was supposed to sit next to you for this.
ごめんなさい 本当は僕から隣の席に座るべきだったのに
That's right.
そうですよ
And also, saying "Please make me happy" wasn't very nice.
それに「僕を幸せにして下さい」はひどいですよ
えっ ひどかったですか
It wasn't?
It was my once-in-a-lifetime proposal. You
shouldn't have placed the focus on yourself.
せっかくの一生に一度のプロポーズなのに「僕を」はないです
Really? Did I do that?
えっ うそ 「僕を」って言いました
I sure messed up.
間違えちゃった
Hiramaru, look.
平丸さん 外
Down there.
あそこ見て
Mr. Yoshida!
吉田氏
I-I want to get off right now and go to him!
は 早く降りたい
吉田氏の所へ
Hiramaru, you really get along well with him, don't you?
平丸さん 吉田さんと本当に仲がいいんですね
Yes! He's like a father to me.
はい 僕の親以上の人なんです
Mr. Yoshida!
吉田氏
You did it, Hiramaru!
よくやった 平丸くん
Mr. Yoshida!
Attention, all visitors.
「ご来場のお客様にお知らせです」
We have a lost item: a ring inside a purple case
「夢の回転コーヒーカップ ピンクの中に」
that was found in the pink cup on the Spin of Dreams teacup ride.
「紫色のケースに入った指輪の落とし物がございました」
What?!
Hiramaru and Aoki got engaged?
平丸さんと蒼樹さんが婚約
Really?
本当ですか
Yeah. It's the talk of the editing department right now.
編集部は今その話題で持ちきりだ
Good for Hiramaru!
やったな 平丸さん
Yeah.
And there's something else they're talking about.
それとは別にもう一つ盛り上がってる話題がある
There is?
もう一つ
It's about the volumes that go on sale today.
今日発売のコミックス第1巻
They're debating which will sell more: Reversi or Zombie Gun?
「REVERSI」と「ZOMBIE☆GUN」どっちが売れるかだ
Both manga got 300,000 copies printed of Volume 1, right?
どっちも初版30万部でしたよね
Right.
そうだ
There were 1.5 million copies printed for CROW,
「CROW」で150万部刷ってた
新妻君の新作としては少ないくらいだが
so it's a comparatively small number for Niizuma.
Having the same number of copies printed as him is a great accomplishment, though.
それと同じ部数というのもすごい事だ
Right!
ですよね
We want to pass 1 million copies of Reversi and become a flagship series in Jack!
俺たちもいつかは100万部いって
「ジャック」の看板になろうぜ
Yeah.
Amazing.
すごいな 発売したばっかりなのに
Even though they just went on sale,
they're already printing another batch of copies for both Zombie Gun and Reversi.
「REVERSI」も「ZOMBIE☆GUN」ももう重版2回目か
Apparently, both of them are flying off the shelves.
どこの書店でも売り切れ続出らしいです で 即重版
So, an immediate reprint.
It's actually kinda cool.
なんか かっこいいですね
Well, I suppose being stuck with too
many copies would be really "uncool."
確かに刷りすぎて余ったとかが一番かっこ悪いもんな
It's Hattori.
服部さんだ 今日何かあったっけ
Was something going on today?
Don't think so.
特には
Hi, this is Takagi.
はい 高木です
I just thought I'd tell you that they're printing yet another batch of copies.
また重版かかったから 教えておこうと思ってな
I see.
そうですか
Thanks for telling us.
わざわざ ありがとうございます
30,000 more?
重版3万
All right!
よしっ
Now we've passed 380,000 in total, right?
これで 累計38万ですね
Last time 50,000, and this time 30,000.
前回5万で 今回は3万
Yes.
Ashirogi Mutou
Two reprints in the ten days since it went on sale. With these kinds of numbers...
発売10日で2回重版して この数字
No, not at all.
It's selling at a way higher pace than TRAP and PCP!
「TRAP」や「PCP」より断然いいペースで売れてる
At this rate, we'll hear talk of an anime soon!
これならアニメ化の話も
Um, Zombie Gun is also getting a reprint, right?
あの 「ZOMBIE☆GUN」も重版するんですよね
Yeah.
How many?
どのくらいですか
It's getting 900,000 more copies.
「ZOMBIE☆GUN」は重版が90万まで決まった
900,000?!
90万
Has it really sold that well so far?
累計で一気にそこまでって事ですか
Niizuma
Eiji
Why is it so much more than Reversi?
何で そんなに「REVERSI」との差が
It's amazing! You've already got 900,000!
すごいよ もう90万部
At this rate, 2 million—No, 3 or 4 million isn't just a dream!
これは200万 いや 300万400万も夢じゃない
4 million is just a dream.
400万は夢です
Huh? It is?
あれ 夢なの
Yes.
はい
Why is Reversi getting higher than you on the rankings, though?
しかし 何でアンケートでは「REVERSI」が上なんだ
Do you know why, Niizuma?
分かるか 新妻君
It's more exciting to read it chapter by chapter.
一回一回の読み応えがあるからですかね
I see.
なるほどね
Which means ours is more interesting to read by the volume!
って事はコミックスで読むと
こっちの方が断然面白いって事か
That's not it, either.
そんな事ないと思いますけど
Huh? Why are we selling much more than them, then?
じゃあ 何で売り上げにこんな差があるんだ
Don't keep asking me these things!
何でもかんでも僕に聞かないで下さい
Sorry.
すまん
Listen up, you two.
いいか 2人とも
Don't panic and head in the wrong direction because you were distracted by Zombie Gun.
「ZOMBIE☆GUN」を意識するあまり
焦って間違った方向に行くのだけは駄目だ
I wanted to know more, so I took a look at the survey results.
僕も気になってアンケート結果を比べてみたんだが
Phone Number
Age
Male
Female
The average reader age of Reversi is higher than Zombie Gun,
平均年齢は「REVERSI」の方が高く
and it's not as popular with female readers.
「ZOMBIE☆GUN」と比べて男女比で
女の子の人気が少ないと出ている
Is the content too difficult for kids to understand?
子供には内容が難しいんでしょうか
It probably is.
そうだな セリフの量も多い
And there's a lot of lines in it, too.
Let's put more effort into concise
dialogue that's easy to understand.
できるだけ分かりやすく簡潔に伝える努力をしていこう
Easy to understand...
分かりやすくですか
Speaking of kids,
子供で思ったんですけど マスコットキャラなんてどうですか
how about we introduce a mascot character?
Is that something you can do with Reversi?
「REVERSI」で出せるか
Maybe a demon in the shape of a cute animal?
例えば動物型のかわいい悪魔とか
In that case, maybe we should put in some breather chapters too.
それなら息継ぎの回があってもいいと思う
"Breather"?
息継ぎ
Yeah. The content is pretty dense every week, right?
毎回 内容が濃いだろ
We could put in some "relaxing"
chapters that kids can easily pick up.
子供にも読みやすい 何て言うか ホッとさせる回
I think that sounds like a good idea.
そういった回はあった方がいい
If you develop the characters more, you can expand the work and create some depth.
キャラを掘り下げたりすれば 作品に広がり 深みもできる
That'll be hard, though.
でも 難しいです
We did decide to head straight for the confrontation between the two protagonists, after all.
主人公2人の対決を一気にってのが基本なので
Yeah.
そうだな
Crap! Why is there such a gap between us?
何でこんなに差がついちゃうんだ
We're giving him a run for his money in the rankings!
アンケートではいい勝負なのに
The biggest difference is that Niizuma's the author of CROW, a long-running flagship series of Jack.
一番大きいのは
「ジャック」で長く看板を張っていた
「CROW」の作者「新妻エイジ」の名前だろうな
It's name recognition.
You're right.
そうですね
There are many people who would buy his volumes in a bookstore
今 本誌を買ってなくても
コミックスが書店に並んでいれば買って
みようって人も多いですよね
even if they don't buy the magazine itself.
That's the difference between
"Ashirogi Mutou" and "Niizuma Eiji."
「亜城木夢叶」と「新妻エイジ」の差か
Well, as you publish more volumes, you may see an increase in sales.
いや 巻を重ねていくうちに 売り上げも伸びるかもしれない
These aren't bad numbers at all for a first volume.
1巻の出だしは決して悪くないんだ
We're nothing to Eiji...
もう エイジには僕たちなんかじゃ
You're right.
As promised, I've continued my series and waited for you.
約束どおり連載続けて待ってました
I'm happy to try hard and compete with you. I won't lose.
競争しながら頑張るのうれしいです 負けないです
Ashirogi and I are fated rivals.
僕と亜城木先生は宿命のライバル 永遠のライバル
Eternal rivals.
「強敵」と書いて「とも」と呼ぶにふさわしい な感じです
Write it as "formidable rival" and read it as "friend"... or something like that.
If any one of you manage to beat me before I start on the manuscript of my final chapter,
僕が最終回の原稿を描く前に
誰であろうと一度でも抜いた人がいたら
then I won't end CROW!
「CROW」はやめません
We're the ones unable to live up to his expectations!
エイジの期待に応えられなかったのは僕たちの方か
Come on, Akito! We never get to go to parties, you know.
ほら秋人さん せっかくのパーティーなんだから
I told you, we're just not in the mood.
俺たち今そんな気分じゃないっつうの
Wow! What a ritzy place!
わぁ～ すごいですね こんな豪華な会場で
That's the Tezuka-Akatsuka Double Prize party for you!
さすが 手塚 赤塚 二大賞パーティー
Indeed.
そうですね
You get an invitation to this every year, right?
毎年招待状は来てたんでしょ
Yeah. We're always busy near the end of the year, so we never ended up going.
年末って忙しいから何だかんだで来られなかった
Invitation card
Yuueisha
2017 Tezuka Akatsuka Prize Winners Party
Ashirogi Mutou
Time
2017 December 11 (Monday)
6 PM
6:30 PM
Place
Grand Hotel reception hall (2nd floor)
Doors open and reception begins
Award commemoration party
Eiji is the judge of the Tezuka prize.
エイジは手塚賞の審査員
He must be here.
きっと会場に来てるはず
Katou is pretty late, though.
それにしても 加藤さん遅いですね
I think she said something about bringing a friend with her.
確か 友達連れてくるって言ってたけど
Sorry I'm late!
すみません 遅くなりました
I'm very thankful you've allowed me to come along!
今日は 無理を言ってご一緒させて頂き
ありがとうございます
Oh, it's nothing.
いえ
I'm Kitami Ririka.
北見リリカです 一応声優の卵やってます
I'm a rookie voice actress.
Voice actress?
声優
Yes.
はい よろしくお願いします
Nice to meet you.
Wow! Are all these people guests?
すごい これ みんな関係者
There are manga artists and stars here, right?
マンガ家さんとか タレントさんとかいるんですよね
I wonder if I can get their autographs.
サインもらってもいいのかな
Definitely not!
駄目
It's not here. I thought as much.
ない やっぱりない
Even though I begged Hattori to submit it,
服部さんに無理を言って出してもらったのに
I didn't even make it to the final round!
最終候補にも残らないとは
It looks like we're free to move around here.
これは終わるまで自由行動の方がいいみたいだな
Orihara just went off somewhere.
折原君もどっか行っちゃったし
He's over there, stuffing his face.
向こうでもうすごい勢いで食べてる
Mr. Mashiro?
真城先生
Yes?
はい
Mr. Takagi is already married,
高木先生はもう結婚してますけど
but do you have a girlfriend?
真城先生は彼女とかいるんですか
Um, yeah.
まあ
Drat. So you do have one.
なんだ やっぱりいるのか
な 何言ってんの リリカ
What are you saying, Ririka?
I'm sorry for her rudeness.
すみません 失礼な事を
Speaking of which,
そういえば 雑誌を見てもしかしてと思ったんですけど
I saw that magazine and I was wondering...
Your girlfriend who came to visit you in the hospital—
病院に来た真城さんの彼女って
She's the really popular voice actress, Azuki Miho, right?
今 大人気の声優の亜豆美保さんですよね
K-Katou!
か 加藤さん
What?!
You're Azukyun's boyfriend, Mashiro?
真城さんってアズキュンの彼氏なんですかぁ
Um, please don't tell anyone.
いや それは誰にも言わないで下さいよ
Oh, what a bummer.
はぁ 残念 世紀のカップルって感じ
It's like they're the couple of the century.
I wanna go home now.
あたし 帰りたくなってきた
Don't be so selfish.
勝手な事ばっかり
What did you come here for in the first place?
っていうか 何しに来たんだ リリカ
Look, Saikou.
見ろよ サイコー
Niizuma's over there, in the middle of a crowd.
あそこの人だかりの中心 新妻さんだぜ
That's crazy. They all must have come to greet him.
すげえな みんな挨拶に来てんだろうな
Looks like it.
だろうな
And those are the anime guys.
で あっちがアニメ関係者
I overheard some bits and pieces.
ちらっと聞いたんだけど「ZOMBIE☆GUN」
もう取り合いになってるみたいだな
Apparently, they're fighting over Zombie Gun.
What? Already?
もう
Yeah.
Niizuma Eiji... Can we pass the Eiji?
新妻エイジ あのエイジを
Can we pass Zombie Gun and become the top manga?
「ZOMBIE☆GUN」を超えて本当にトップになれるのか
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Tezuka
Prize
Judge
Niizuma
Eiji
Ashirogi! It's been a Bleach long while!
亜城木先生 お久しBLEACHです
Yes, it has.
お久しぶりです
G-Good evening.
こ こんばんは
Reversi is really good!
「REVERSI」面白いです 本当にウルトラ面白いです
It's really ultra good!
I'm always losing to you in the rankings! The readers know a good one when they see it!
アンケートも負けてばかりみたいですし 読者の目は確かです
Especially these past few weeks! That's Ashirogi for you!
特にここ数週間は さすが亜城木先生です
Th-Thanks.
ど どうも
But I won't lose.
でも負けません アンケートでも上にいってみせます
I'll go higher than you in the rankings.
And I definitely won't lose to you in the number of copies sold!
そしてコミックスの部数でも絶対に負けませんから
Niizuma...
新妻さん
I'm back. I got you whatever looked good.
お待たせ とりあえずおいしいもの見繕ってきたよ
Thanks!
どうもです あと何食べてないですかね
What haven't I eaten yet?
I'm glad we came, Shuujin.
来てよかったよ シュージン
Eiji said he won't lose to us in the number of copies we sell.
エイジ コミックスの部数でも負けないって言ってくれたじゃん
He said he won't lose, even though he's selling so many more than us!
「ZOMBIE☆GUN」が圧倒的に
勝ってるコミックスの部数でも「負けない」って
Because he thinks we're going to make a comeback at this rate!
このままだと逆転されるかもしれないと思ってるから
Yeah!
That must be it!
間違ってない
We just have to head towards the ending
俺たちはラストに向けて
黒と白の対決を毎週面白く描き続ければいいんだ
while making the confrontation between white and black as interesting as we can every single week!
Yeah!
だな 必ず差は縮まる
We'll definitely close that gap!
Um...
あのう ちょっとよろしいでしょうか
Can I speak to you for a moment?
Um, sure.
はい
Excuse me, but you are Ashirogi, correct?
失礼ですが 亜城木先生ですよね
That's right. Can we help you?
そうですけど 何か
I am very pleased to meet you.
お初にお目にかかります 私 こういう者ですが
I work for this company.
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
Tanabe Futoshi
Producer
Animation production studio
do
u
shi
te
da
ro...
i
tsu
mo
so
u
sa
Why, I wonder?
chi
ka
zu
ku
ta
bi
ka
ra
ma
wa
ri
no
yu
me
Whenever I am close to fulfilling my goals, all effort becomes fruitless
ma
e
wo
mu
i
te
shi
ga
mi
tsu
i
te
sou
su
ko
shi
zu
tsu
We walk ahead, hold each other, and with little things
ya
ku
so
no
a
ba
sho
he
to
sa
e
ai
na
ga
ra
we support each other to reach what we promised
ji
shi
n
ga
ta
ri
na
i
to
ki
wa
mu
ne
ni
te
wo
a
te
When we lack confidence, we put a hand to our heart
bo
ku
ra
ga
tsu
zu
t
ta
pe
e
ji
yo
mi
ka
e
so
u
and reread the pages we assembled into a story
kyo
u
ma
de
so
shi
te
a
su
he
to
tsu
zu
i
te
yu
ku
no
sa
They lead up to today and continue into the morrow
ta
i
se
tsu
na
yu
me
ga
ka
na
u
so
no
hi
ma
de
We will always be ourselves
a
ri
no
ma
bo
ku
ra
de
zu
tto...
until the day that our dreams come true
Next Time
Preview
Making a work you're happy with!
納得できる作品を作りたい
That is the pride of a manga artist!
それがマンガ家の誇り
Can you get away with saying that, Hattori?
そんなこと言ってていいのか 服部
Hot Springs and
Confirmation
Next time: Hot Spring and Confirmation.
次回 温泉と意思確認
誇りと夢のどっちを取るんだ
Which will you choose: pride or dreams?